Guide to the Gerard Salton papers
Salton, Gerard papers
- Series IV. Professional Papers Writings Books
  - Niklaus Writh and Helmut Weber "Euler: A Generalized of Algol and its Formal Definition" (Box 62, Folder 56)
  - N. Wirth, Lilith Computer (Box 62, Folder 57)
  - M. Wirth, Modula (Box 62, Folder 58)
  - Wirth, Niklaus, The Programming Language Pascal, November 1970 (Box 62, Folder 59)
  - Wiswesser, W.J., Small Chemical Data Systems (Box 62, Folder 60)
  - Wiswesser, William J.: A Decoding Study of the Line-Formula Chemical Notation (Box 62, Folder 61)
  - L. Wittgenstein's Philosophical Investigations (Box 62, Folder 62)
  - Wolfe, Theodore, An Evaluation of On-Line Information Retrieval System Techniques (Box 62, Folder 63)
  - Wolfe-Terroine, M. & Rimbert, D., Computer-Aided Automatic Generation of a Structured Documentary Language: Preliminary Study (Box 62, Folder 64)
  - E. Wong and K. Youssefi, Decomposition, Query Processing (Box 62, Folder 65)
  - S.K.M. Wong, Y.Y. Yao, Z.W. Wang, Analysis of Vector Space Models (Box 62, Folder 66)
  - E. Wong and R.H. Katz, Design Goals for Relational and DBTG Databases (Box 62, Folder 67)
  - S.K.M. Wong, Entropy Similarity Measure (Box 62, Folder 68)
  - S.K.M. Wong, W. Ziarko, V.V. Raghavan, P.C.N. Wong, Extending Vector Space to Boolean (Box 62, Folder 69)
  - S.K.M. Wong, Ziarko, Raghavan, Wong, Info Retrieval Concepts (Box 62, Folder 70)
  - S.K.M. Wong and Y.Y. Yao, Linear Structure in IR (Box 62, Folder 71)
  - S.K.M. Wong and Y.Y. Yao Linear Structure in IR (Box 62, Folder 72)
  - S.K.M. Wong, Generalized Models for IR (Box 62, Folder 73)
  - S.K.M Wong and Y.Y. Yao, Probalistic Inference Model (Box 62, Folder 74)
  - S.K.M. Wong and Y.Y. Yao, Prob. Inference Model for IR (Box 62, Folder 75)
  - S.K.M. Wong, G. Salton, and Y.Y. Yao, Relevance Feedback based on an Adaptive Linear Model (Box 62, Folder 76)
  - S.K.M. Wong, Reprints (Box 62, Folder 77)
  - S.K.M. Wong and Y.Y. Yao, A Statistical Similarity Measure (Box 62, Folder 78)
  - Thesis-Studies on Clustered Files, YCA Wong (Box 62, Folder 79)
  - Wood, Gary Richard: Application of a Restructable Computer System to Numerical Weather Prediction Computations (Box 62, Folder 80)
  - W.A. Woods, Augmented Transition Networks (Box 62, Folder 81)
  - Woodrum, L.J., Sorting w/ Minimal Comparing (Box 62, Folder 82)
  - The Defense Documentation Center Natural Enlgish Preprocessor (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Woods, William A., An Experimental Parsing System for Transition Network Grammers (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - W.A. Woods, Knowldege Representation (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Woods, W.A., Procedural Semantics for a Question-Answering Machine (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Woods, W.A. Transition Network Grammers for Natural Language Analysis (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - W. Woods, Speech Understanding Systems (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - W.M. A. Woods and J.G. Schmolze, The KL-ONE Family (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - W.A. Woods, Procedural Semantics for Q-A (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Woods, William, Context-Sensitive Parsing (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Woods, William A. Jr., A Mathematical Theory of Information Retrieval Systems (AM 221, Fall 1964) (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - W.M. A. Woods, Syntax Semantics + Speech (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Wooster, H., D-434, Info Analysis Center Effectiveness Chrestomathy (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Wooster, H. D-435, MIcrofiche 1969-User Survey (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Word Net (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Word Processing (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Word Statistics (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Worona, S., A Systematic Study of Query-Clustering Techniques: A Progress Report (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Technical Writing (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - H. Wu and G. Salton, Term Relevance vs. IDF (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - H. Wu, Query Formulation in Info Retrieval (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - H. Wu, Utility Theory (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - M.F. Wyle, Automatic Indexing (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Wulf, W.A. et al Bliss Ref. Manual, A Basic Language for Implementation of System Software for the PDP-10 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Wyllys, R.E., Automatic Analysis of the Contents of Documents (I and II) (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - R.E. Wyllys, Automatic Abstracting Procedures (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Wysocki, A. and Tocatlian, J., A World Science Information System Necessary and Feasible (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - X Con System for Computer Configuration (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - X Terminal (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Xerox Parc (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - R. Yager, Weighted Queries (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Yakushin, B.V., Algorithmic Method of Discriminating Subject Concepts for Index Compilation (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Yale University Restructuring (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Directory Design and Record Allocation for List and Cluster Files (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - C.S. Yang and C.F. Yu, Best Match Querying (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Y. Yang and C.G. Chute, Example-Based Mapping (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Y. Yang and C.G. Chute, Linear Least Square Fit (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Yanov, Yu. I., On Transformations of Program Flow Diagrams (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Y. Y. Yao, User Preference of Documents (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Yilman, Huseyin, On Color Perception (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - M. K. Yip, An Expert System for Document Retrieval (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - M. Yitzhaki, Language Barrier (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Yngve, Victor H., COMIT as an IR Language (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Yngve, Victor H., The COMIT System for Mechanical Translation (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Yngve, Victor H., Computer Programs for Translation (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Yngve, Victor H., Computer Programs for Translation (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Yngve, Victor H., A Model and an Hypothesis for Language Structure (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Yngve, Victor H., MT at M.I.T. 1965 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Yngve, Victor H., A Programming Language for Mechanical Translation (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Yngve, Victor H., Some Applications of Computers in Linguistics (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Young, J. W., and Kent, H.K., Abstract Formulations of Data Processing Problems (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - C.T. Yu, M.K. Siu, K. Lam, F. Tai, Adaptive Clustering Schemes (Box 63, Folder 51)
  - Yu, C.T., and Luk, W.S., Analysis of Effectiveness of Retrieval in Clustered Files (Box 63, Folder 52)
  - Yu, C.T., Application of BLE Approximation (Box 63, Folder 53)
  - Yu, C.T., The Stability of Two Common Matching Functions in Classification with Respect to a Proposed Measure (Box 63, Folder 54)
  - Yu, C.T. and Johnson, D.T., On the Complexity of Finding the Set of Candidate Keys for a Given Set of Functional Dependencies (Box 63, Folder 55)
  - Yu, C.T., Computer Algorithms for FR (Box 63, Folder 56)
  - C.T. Yu and D. Chow, Constructive Feedback Query (Box 63, Folder 57)
  - Yu, C.T., Methodology for Term Classes (Box 63, Folder 58)
  - C. Liv and C.T. Yu, Data Comprehension Using Word Encoding (Box 63, Folder 59)
  - C.T. Yu and M. Ozsoyoglu, Distributed Query (Box 63, Folder 60)
  - Yu, Clem, A Formal Construction of Term Classes (Box 63, Folder 61)
  - C.T. Yu, W. Meng, and S. Park, Framework for Effective Retrieval (Box 63, Folder 62)
  - C.T. Yu, W.S. Luk, and M.K. Siu, On the Estimation of the Number of Desired Records with Respect to a Given Query (Box 63, Folder 63)
  - Yu, C.T., Models for Constructing Optimal Queries (Box 63, Folder 64)
  - C.T. Yu, W.S. Luk, and M.K. Sui, Models of IR Processes (Box 63, Folder 65)
  - C.T. Yu and T.C. Lee, Non-Binary Independence Model (Box 63, Folder 66)
  - C.T. Yu, Z.M. Ozsoyoglu and M.K. Siu, Parallelism in Data Base Systems (Box 63, Folder 67)
  - C.T. Yu, Lam, C. Hung, Probalistic Retrieval (Box 63, Folder 68)
  - C.T. Yu and F.Y. Chin, Protection of Statistical Data Bases (Box 63, Folder 69)
  - Yu, Clem and Raghavan, Vijay, A Single Pass Method for Determining the Semantic Relationships Between Terms (Box 63, Folder 70)
  - Yu, C.T., On a Partitioning Problem (Box 63, Folder 71)
  - C.T. Yu, W.S. Luk, and T.Y. Cheung, Statistical Model of Relevance Feedback (Box 63, Folder 72)
  - Yu, C.T., Statistical Relevance Feedback Model (Box 63, Folder 73)
  - C.T. Yu and Olta Stemming Revisited (Box 63, Folder 74)
  - Yu, C.T., Theory of Indexing and Classification (Box 63, Folder 75)
  - Project Updates, June 1992 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Zachary N., A First Memorandum on the Plans of the Harvard University Computing Center (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Zadeh, L.A., The Dilemma of Computer Sciences (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Fuzzy Logic (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Zakrevskii, A.D., A Vistual-Matrix Method for Minimizing Boolean Functions (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Zamora, A., Correction of Spelling Errors in a Large Data Base (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Zamora, A. and Hamill, K.A., Titles for Automatic Document Classification (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Rebsamen, Reimer, Ursprung, Zehnder, A Data Base System for the Personal Computer Lilith (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Zemanek, H., Electronische Rechenanlagen Geschichte des Automation: Fruhgeschichte (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Zemanek, H., Was ist Informatik? (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Zhang, Y. and Salton, G., Enhancement of Text Representations Using Related Document Titles (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Zhang, D., OCR Data Corruption (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Zhang, D., Z39.50 User Interface Project (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Zhou, J., Term Dependency and P-Values (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Ziman, J.M., Information, Communication, Knowledge (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Ziman, J.M., Proliferation of Scientific Literature: A Natural Process (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Zimmerman, R.G.J., A Computer-Accessed Microfiche Library (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Zimmerman, H.U., CTX Indexing System (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Zimmerman, H., Textverarbeitung mit Abitur (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Ziv, J. and Lempel, A., Universal Algorithm for Sequential Data Comression (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Zloof, M. and de Jong, S.P., Business Automation (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Zloof, M.M., QBE/OBE Business Language (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Zloof, M.M., Query by Example: Operations on Hierarchical Data Bases (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Zobel, Moffat, Wilkinson, Sacks-Davis, Efficient Retrieval of Partial Documents (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Zull, C.G. and Baumanis, G.J., Textual Correlations of Relevance: Preliminary Investigations (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Zunde, P. and Dexter, M.E., Indexing Consistency and Quality (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Zuse, K., Über den Plankalkül (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Zunde, P., Theories of Information (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Zunde, P. and Gehl, J., Theories of Information Science, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - Zwicky, Friedman, Hall, and Walker, The MITRE Syntactic Analysis Procedure for Transformational Grammers (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - ZyLab Corporation (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - Book Collection, Part I (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Book Collection, Part II (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - Clustering Experiments: Disk Allocation Maps (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - Clustering Experiments: Special SMART Load Modules (Box 64, Folder 35)
  - Clustering Experiments: SMART Manuals and Other Literature (Box 64, Folder 36)
  - Clustering Experiments: Possible SMART Collections on Tape (Box 64, Folder 37)
  - Clustering Experiments: Concordance Table Sorter (Box 64, Folder 38)
  - Clustering Experiments: Wordform Lookform (Box 64, Folder 39)
  - Clustering Experiments: JCL (Box 64, Folder 40)
  - Clustering Experiments: Lockstem, Wordstem (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Clustering Experiments: HASP (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Clustering Experiments: PL/1; PL/C (Box 64, Folder 43)
  - Clustering Experiments: Discrimination Value Programs (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - Clustering Experiments: Assorted Short Programs (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Clustering Experiments: Waterloo (Box 64, Folder 46)
  - Clustering Experiments: SSP Statistical Routines (Box 64, Folder 47)
  - Clustering Experiments: Johnson and Lafuente Cluster Program (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - Clustering Experiments: Kargman/Herzog (Box 64, Folder 49)
  - Clustering Experiments: Air Force (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Clustering Experiments: Dance, Dennis (University of Arkansas) (Box 64, Folder 51)
  - Clustering Experiments: University of California Berkeley (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - Clustering Experiments: Berne (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - Clustering Experiments: MBH Bonn (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - Clustering Experiments: Bowling Green State University (Box 64, Folder 55)
  - Clustering Experiments: Brown University (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - Clustering Experiments: City University of New York (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - Clustering Experiments: Eldg. Technische Hochschule (Box 64, Folder 58)
  - Clustering Experiments: ISPRA (Box 64, Folder 59)
  - Clustering Experiments: University of Lagos (Nigeria), Alice B. Oke (Box 64, Folder 60)
  - Clustering Experiments: M.I.T. (Box 64, Folder 61)
  - Clustering Experiments: University of North Carolina (Box 64, Folder 62)
  - Clustering Experiments: Northeastern Illinois University (Box 64, Folder 63)
  - Clustering Experiments: Queen's University (Box 64, Folder 64)
  - Clustering Experiments: Rhode Island (Box 64, Folder 65)
  - Clustering Experiments: General Motors (Box 64, Folder 66)
  - Clustering Experiments: Texas A&M (Box 64, Folder 67)
  - Clustering Experiments: Wisconsin State University and Nebraska University (Box 64, Folder 68)
  - Clustering Experiments (Box 64, Folder 69)
  - Clustering Experiments and Articles (Box 64, Folder 70)
  - LINIX Tools/Commands (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Maps, Algorithms (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Maps, Algorithms (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Notes and Revisions/Maps/Algorithms (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Revisions/Maps/Algorithms (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents) (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents) (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents), Evaluation 9600 G's (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents) (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents), Path Analysis (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents), Project References (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Paths in Segments (Patents), Top Ranked Evaluation (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, Segments Themes (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 44600 Patent (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 28965 Patent (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 30793 Patent (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 43217 Patent (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 35557 Patent (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 1568 Patent (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 1456 Patent (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 262 Patent (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 1525 Patent (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 2692 Patent (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 4239 Patent (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 32213 Patent (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 28413 Patent (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 32596 Patent (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 996 Patent (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 2454 Patent (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 43217 Patent (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, Comparisons (Early Local Global) (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 30793 Patent (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, 34263 Patent (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, Patents (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, Patents, Runs (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Segments Federal Regulations, Federal Register (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Kuwait and the Oil Market (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Segments, Msoft (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Segments, Msoft (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Segments, Msoft (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Segments, Msoft, Gapping Notes (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Segments, Msoft, 347 African Literature (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Segments, Msoft, 534 Albania (Box 65, Folder 43)
  - Segments, Msoft, 661 Msoft Algerbra (Box 65, Folder 44)
  - Segments, Msoft, 661 (Box 65, Folder 45)
  - Segments, Msoft, 859 American Revolution (Box 65, Folder 46)
  - 859 American Revolution Data (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - 952 Anatomy Data (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - 952 Anatomy Data (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - 1397 Arithmetic Data (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - 4304 Carrier Data (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - 17016 Nuclear Weapons Data (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - 21385 Smoking Data (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - 24411 World War I Data (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Segments, Themes, Wall Street Journal (Box 66, Folder 9-11)
  - Segment Similarities (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Segment Similarities: Slides (CS 739) (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Segment Similarites: Summaries (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Segmentation Summaries (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Segmentation Summaries: Spanish Collection (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Text Sorts: Caesar Internal (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Text Sorts: 4099 Caesar (mixed) (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Text Sorts: 5539 Civil War (internal) (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Text Sorts: 9620 Gandhi (internal) (Box 66, Folder 20)
  - Text Sorts: 9667 Garrison (mixed) (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Text Sorts: Long Documents Excerpts (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Text Sorts: mixed (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Text Sorts: mixed maps (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Text Sorts: mixed subjects-text (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Text Sorts: Napoleonic Wars (multi-section items) (Box 66, Folder 26)
  - Text Sorts: Napoleonic Wars (internal) (Box 66, Folder 27)
  - Text Sorts: Nuclear Weapons (internal) (Box 66, Folder 28)
  - Text Sorts: Shakespeare Sonnets (Box 66, Folder 29)
  - Text Sorts: Clustered Items (Box 66, Folder 30)
  - Text Sorts: Tipster Domain (Box 66, Folder 31)
  - Text Sorts: TREL 4 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  - Text Sorts: Tours of Federal Register (Box 66, Folder 33)
  - Text Sorts: Typed links (Box 66, Folder 34)
  - Paragraph searches (Box 66, Folder 35)
  - Data printouts (Box 66, Folder 36-39)
  - Miscellaneous paperwork (Box 66, Folder 40)
  - Bound data printout: Context Strings (Box 67)
  - Data printouts (Box 67, Folder 1-13)
  - Notes on Comparing Statistically and Syntactically Generated Term Phrases (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Word List (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Birthday Card from G. Salton, Mar. 9, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Joy, William An Introduction to the C Shell (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Noun phrases (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - SIFT Review (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Runs: Tape information (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Runs: How to do it - hints for SMART (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Runs: SMART (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Runs: cacm.result (Box 67, Folder 23)
  - Runs: Result analysis (Box 67, Folder 24)
  - Runs: USA retrieval runs (Box 67, Folder 25)
  - Runs: USA (text) (Box 67, Folder 26)
  - Runs: USA I overall results (Box 67, Folder 27)
  - Run Lists: Document pairs .35 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  - Run Lists: Summary run list for textbook (Box 67, Folder 29)
  - Run Lists: Run 21 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  - Run Lists: Run 31 (Box 67, Folder 31)
  - Run Lists: Run 31, 21, sd, 2sd (Box 67, Folder 32)
  - Run Lists: Run 35, 36 (no phrases) (Box 67, Folder 33)
  - Run Lists: newdocs output (Box 67, Folder 34)
  - Run Lists: Comparisons for sentence pairs (old 500 comparison) (Box 67, Folder 35)
  - 3-31 comparison (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Comparison between sentence pairs (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - 3 single SD, double SD (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - 19 single, double SD (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - 3-19 Comarison (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Run 19: Top 2400 Sentences (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Run 24 and 2400 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Run 15 and 30 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - 10 Query output for paragraphs in books (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - 10 Query output, book (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Runs 25 and 2400 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Runs 31 and 19: Global (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Runs 31-17: Document output sentence match (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Run 17: single and double SD (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Runs 31-36 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Run 18: Top 2400 sentences (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Run 17: Top 2400 sentences (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - 31-18: General sentence comparison (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Chris Buckley (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - 31-3: Comparison document output (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - 3-21: SD 2 Set output (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - 3-24: Comparison SD, 2 SD (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - Run 16: Overall output (old) (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - Global comparison, book paragraphs (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - 31-35 Comparisons, doc-doc (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Run 20: Top 2400 sentences, Nov. 15, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 26)
  - Documents joined by several links, Sep. 7, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 27)
  - Global sentence all terms, Sep. 28, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 28)
  - Run 9: Sentence matches in Toy 500 document, Sep. 27, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 29)
  - Top 500 pairs of Documents, sentences indexed using 5 best terms, phrases included (Box 68, Folder 30)
  - Pairs with run comparison (Box 68, Folder 31)
  - 35-21 doc-doc output, SD, 2SD (Box 68, Folder 32)
  - Run 13: all terms, 500 sentence pairs, Oct. 5, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 33)
  - 31-19: document output via global sentences or via sentences in documents, Dec. 7, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 34)
  - 31-19: sentence output comparison, Dec. 7, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 35)
  - Run 32: Sentence links in top2400 doc-pairs, Dec. 7, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 36)
  - Run 28: Sentence limits for top 2400 doc-pairs, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 37)
  - Comparison for doc-doc output (old 500 comparison), Oct. 5, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 38)
  - 28-25: 2SD Document comparison, top 10 ntc terms and phrases, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 39)
  - 28-21: ntc doc pairs, 2SD, Dec. 6, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - 28-19: Sentences in top 10 ntc documents, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - 28-25: Doc top 10 terms and phrases vs. doc-pairs with matching sentences, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - 28-17: Sentences Global top 2400 (top ntc terms and phrases) vs. sentences occuring in top 2400 ntc doc-pairs, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - 28-26 Comparison, sentences occuring in top 2400 ntc doc-pairs vs. all terms and phrases, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - Run 26: Sentence links for top 2400 ntc doc-pairs, Dec. 1, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - Run 22 (old 9): Top 2400 doc and sentences, Nov. 15, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - Run 23: Sentences for Run 21 2400 ntc docs, Nov. 15, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - Global document matches, 21-24, 21-25, 24-25, Nov. 16, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 48)
  - Run 21 (old 8): Top 2400 doc-pairs ntc (Box 68, Folder 49)
  - Evaluation 60 doc-pairs, Dec. 1989-Jan. 1990 (Box 68, Folder 50)
  - Run 31: 2SD, large size output (Box 68, Folder 51)
  - 31-24: SD output (Box 68, Folder 52)
  - 35-36: In-sentence similarity, Jan. 16, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 53)
  - 31-35: dd output sentence matches, Dec. 12, 1989 (Box 68, Folder 54)
  - New run list, overall, Feb. 8, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  - 21-24: Comparison doc-doc ntc (Box 68, Folder 56)
  - Schedules (Box 68, Folder 57)
  - Restrictions (Runs) (Box 68, Folder 58)
  - Student Results: Buckley, Chris (Box 68, Folder 59)
  - Student Results: Buckley, extra term weights (Box 68, Folder 60)
  - Student Results: Dabney, Dan (Box 68, Folder 61)
  - Student Results: Gries, David (Box 68, Folder 62)
  - Student Results: Ellen, business correspondence, May 18, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 63)
  - Student Results: Fos, E., parameter interactions (Box 68, Folder 64)
  - Student Results: Hooper, Robert, Nov. 19, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 65)
  - Student Results: Jacobs, Paul, Text Based Intelligent Systems (Box 68, Folder 66)
  - Student Results: Lee, Joon Ho (Box 68, Folder 67)
  - Student Results: Levine, Emile, ASIS, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 68)
  - Student Results: SKIP's concordance program write-up (Box 68, Folder 69)
  - Runs: Student Results: Doug Smith work (clustering experiments) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Runs: Student Results: Steve Tomlinson (Box 69, Folder 2)